TROY VASSALOTTI

2700 Remington Ave, Apt. 312, Baltimore, MD 21211 ♦ (240) 446-7613 ♦ troyvassalotti@gmail.com

https	://actionhamilton.github.io/
PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY Driven and dedicated marketer with a passion for design, programming, and optimized organization. Quick learner, always ready to broaden my skills and knowledge. Expertise includes inbound, email, and content marketing, responsive web design, and data reporting and analysis.	
Email Marketing	Graphic Design
 Content Marketing 	 Google G-Suite
 Inbound Marketing 	 Microsoft Office
• SEO	 Adobe Premiere Pro
• HTML & CSS	• GitHub Atom
 Google Analytics 	 JavaScript
 Adobe Photoshop 	 Project Management

Marketing Production Coordinator, 09/2017 to Current

Terra's Kitchen – Baltimore, MD

• Design and build HTML and drag-and-drop promotional, transactional, and automated emails in HubSpot.

WORK HISTORY -

- Analyze email channel performance regularly to assess trends and test further optimizations.
- Research keywords for content creation and implementation to improve SEO.
- Create additional product offerings within our eCommerce platform, Magento.
- Edit select web page and blog content with updates as needed.
- Take part in QA of website updates such as new purchase funnels and customer account features.

Songwriter, Guitarist, 03/2014 to Current

Front Royal – Damascus, MD

- Market and promote the band through associated social media pages.
- Build my network of local bands and promoters to create and play concerts.
- Completed two independent summer tours across 11 states.
- Work on production and editing of online video content.

Bakery Service and Production, 03/2013 to 05/2017

Weis Markets Inc – Damascus, MD

- File orders, inventories, and invoices for transactions in the period.
- Act as manager-on-duty and run bakery while active managers are off.

EDUCATION

B.S., Business Administration: Marketing, 2017

Towson University - Towson, MD

- GPA: 3.48/4.0
- Dean's List 2 semesters

CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Office Towson University
- Inbound Marketing HubSpot
- Email Marketing HubSpot
- Content Marketing HubSpot
- $\bullet \ Responsive \ Web \ Design-freeCodeCamp.org$
- SEO Training Course Moz